Vengeance for the right price.
Dead for a Dollar is a western, thriller, action film directed by Walter Hill.
In 1897, veteran bounty hunter Max Borlund is deep into Mexico where he encounters professional
gambler and outlaw Joe Cribbens — a sworn enemy he sent to prison years before.
Max is on a mission to find and return Rachel Kidd, the wife of a wealthy businessman, who as
the story is told to Max, has been abducted by Buffalo Soldier Elijah Jones.
Max is ultimately faced with a showdown to save honor.
Max Borlund, played by Christoph Waltz.
Joe Cribbens, played by Willem Dafoe.
Rachel Kidd, played by Rachel Brosnahan.
Martin Kidd, played by Hamish Linklater.
Tiberio Vargas, played by Benjamin Bratt.
English Bill, played by Guy Burnet.
Dead for a Dollar is a 2022 American western action thriller
film written and directed by Walter Hill.
It stars Christoph Waltz, Willem Dafoe, and Rachel Brosnahan.
The plot follows a bounty hunter (Waltz) on a search to find
the missing wife (Brosnahan) of a businessman.
Brandon Scott, Warren Burke, Benjamin Bratt, and Hamish Linklater also star.
The film premiered out of competition at the 79th Venice
International Film Festival on September 6, 2022.
It was released in the United States on September
30, 2022, by Quiver Distribution.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.